Ji Ming.
Xiaoyu.
It's time to go home.
The baby is hungry.
Rules
are set for the lower class.
You've overstepped.
It's fake.
Everything is fake.
How dare you lie to me!
Ah!
Hello?
Didn't you
come to the office today?
I'm dealing with some matters at the law firm.
How about we have dinner together tonight?
Sorry,
I'm really not free today.
I have a meeting scheduled for tonight.
I'm hanging up now.
Mr. Lin,
here are the roses
and birthday card you asked me to buy.
Oh,
put them here.
I've terminated the agency.
Bai Qiang is suspected of criminal offenses.
I can't get involved in this case.
Did that brainless Bai Qiang
say something she shouldn't have?
Sister Wei
The business of S club
is out of the line.
Out of the line?
Vivian
Don't forget
how you had the chance to get close to Lin Jiming.
That's how this circle works.
Everyone takes what they need.
Bai Qiang is stupid.
She exposed herself.
Why blame me?
I didn't mean that.
If the case of Niudingshan is dug deeper,
the club will be involved.
You need to make a plan.
You are
the favorite of the Lin Group.
You can't even handle this little thing for me?
Besides,
Mr. Wen...
Mr. Wen is Mr. Wen,
and I am me.
Wei,
we
are in the same boat.
Ah.
Mr. Wen
seems to be interested in you recently.
He asked me a lot about you.
He looked like a father who was looking for a daughter-in-law.
Mr. Wen?
What did he ask?
Nothing much.
Just some
of your performances
during your training at the club.
Oh.
He also took your photo for plastic surgery evaluation.
Wang Jiming,
don't blame me.
You should
blame your bad luck
for being born in the wrong family.
Jiming
is the one who truly inherits everything from the Lin family.
He must
take that position
cleanly and fairly.
It will be a mutual support.
Who knows?
It's also for the sake of the ill-fated couple.
From now on,
he is the son of Lin Muyun,
Lin Jiming.
You're just his driver.
Understand?
But he is our...
Can you give him a bright future?
He can only live a better life
as the heir of the Lin family.
Zhan Shan,
Jiming can't hold this position
depends on
whether we are ruthless enough.
Gu Qingyu,
you really shouldn't have come back.
Three years ago,
you escaped a disaster.
This time,
you're really not that lucky.
Lin Jiming.
Jiming.
Wake up.
Lin Jiming.
Jiming.
Wake up.
It's you.
Who is the family member?
-How is he?  -I am.
He got a forehead injury.
He got 7 stitches.
He has a mild concussion.
His left radius is fractured.
Now,
it has been fixed.
But
he lost a lot of blood.
He needs a blood transfusion.
But
the patient is Rh-negative.
We don't have enough
Rh-negative blood in the blood bank.
We need to
get it from the blood station in the city center.
It may
take some time.
I'm Rh-negative.
I can do it.
Take mine.
You too?
Ah.
Are you the patient's...
I...
I'm their driver.
I watched him grow up.
Doctor,
saving lives is the priority.
I'm healthy, no problem.
Alright.
In that case,
you can go with the nurse
to do a cross-matching test.
Ah.
Fortunately,
the patient's internal organs and brain are not injured.
You can go through the procedures.
The patient has Rh-negative blood.
I have Rh-negative blood.
Draw mine.
Are you the patient's...
I... I'm their driver.
I watched him grow up.
Wu Zhanshan.
His family was a bit better off at the time.
They helped Shiyi's family a lot.
Oh my.
They're a pair of star-crossed lovers.
I heard
the car accident victim who was just brought in
has Rh-negative blood.
That's right.
Rh-negative, the so-called "panda blood".
Fortunately, the man who came with him
has the same blood type.
It's really fortunate.
Otherwise, getting blood from the bank would be troublesome.
Oh,
he's also Rh-negative.
What a coincidence.
This blood type has a strong genetic predisposition.
It's more likely to occur among immediate family members.
I guess that's his father.
From the perspective of genetics,
if the parents are Rh-negative,
the children are basically the same.
The probability is much lower between non-relatives.
The effect of anesthetic has not completely worn off.
I guess he can wake up when it's light.
I guess that's his father.
From a genetic point of view,
if parents are Rh-negative,
their children are basically the same.
The probability between non-relatives is much lower.
It's Wen Shiyi who asked you to do this, right?
She asked you to kill me.
Wu Zhanshan,
you almost killed your own son.
How do you feel?
I didn't.
Don't talk nonsense.
Lin Jiming
is not the son of Lin Muyun.